

Erick Alejandro Fernández Bustos

Software Engineer

- erickalejandrofernandez@amail.com 📞 +593998667053

Profile

I am a software engineer with a strong background in information technology, specialized in the design, architecture, development and maintenance of web, mobile and desktop applications. My work involves applying my technical expertise and creativity to address and solve both new challenges and current problems that arise in the technology arena. I use software engineering principles as my guide to ensure that the solutions I develop are efficient, reliable and scalable, thus contributing to the success and innovation in diverse projects.

Education

Software Engineer

ESPE, Latacunga

Consumer electronics

Ramón Barba Naranjo, Latacunga

march 2019 – september 2023

september 2009 – july 2015

Experience

Backend Engineer

ADS Software, Latacunga

Frontend Engineer

Seeds Ecuador, Salcedo

march 2022 - june 2022

september 2021 – december 2021

Languajes

English language proficiency

Level B1 of the Common European Framework.

Aptitudes

- Organization
- Teamwork
- Proactivity
- Self-learning
- Leadership
- Responsibility
- Commitment
- Involvement

Skills

Programming languages:	Non-relational databases:	Others:
C++	Firebase	Cloud computing
Assembler	MongoDB	Software quality models
Java	CouchDB	Software architecture
HTLM	Redis	Software testing
PHP	Databases in the cloud:	Docker y kubernetes
C#	Azure	Machine Learning
Python	AWS	Computersecurity
Flutter	Oracle Cloud	Deep Learning
nonei	Networks:	Artificial Intelligence
Java\$cript	WAN	Systems analysis and design
Frameworks:	LAN	ERP
React	Video games:	Usability
Vue	Unity	UX
Laravel	Unreal engine	Office
Relational databases:	Methodologies:	OS:
Microsoft SQL Server	SCRUM en DGS	Windows
Oracle	DevOps	Мас
DB2	XP Extreme programming	Linux
PostgreSQL	Kanban	Repositories:
MariaDB		Git